Guide to the Yale Daily News Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographic negatives used in the publication of the Yale Daily News, 1957-1982; Series I
  - 1977
    - 1977 March 3 - April 26
      - Lacrosse v. U Conn, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Men and Women's Track Meet, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Lacrosse v. Wesleyan, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Top Women Tennis Players, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Women's Lacrosse Practice, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Baseball v. New haven, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Women's Tennis Practice, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Men's Tennis, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Baseball v. S. Conn, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Sports: Golfers, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Trinity, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Baseball/Lacrosse v. Princeton, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Lacrosse v. Penn, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Synchronized Swimming, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Yale Precision Swimming Band, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - 1977 September 10-29
      - Football v. CW Post, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Men's Tennis Tryouts, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Football v. Brown, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Soccer v. Brown, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Football v, U Conn, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Sunday- City Series Soccer, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Soccer, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Women's Tennis, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Women's Field Hockey v. Springfield, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Women's Soccer Practice, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Volleyball Practice, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Field Hockey v. Williams, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - 1977 October 1-31
      - Illegal cooking in rooms, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Women's Soccer v. Williams, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Football v. Miami, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Field Hockey v. Smith, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Tailgate Parties at Dartmouth Game, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Rugby v. Dartmouth, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Women's Soccer v. Tufts, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Field Hockey vs. Dartmouth, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Women's Ice Hockey, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Women's Tennis v. Smith, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Football v. Columbia, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Volleyball Practice, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Water Polo, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Field Hockey v. Conn Col., 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Soccer v. Penn, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Field Hockey v. Penn, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Football v. Penn, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Bladderball, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Field Hockey v. SCSC, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Women's Field Hockey, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Water Polo Tournament, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Football v. Cornell, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Water Polo v. Brown; Finals, 1977 October (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - 1977 November 2-30
      - Tang Cup football championships, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Field Hockey v. Radcliffe, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Football v. Princeton, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Soccer v. Princeton, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Soccer v. Intramural Athletics, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Football v. Harvard, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Hockey v. St Lawrence, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Hockey v. Penn, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Hockey v. Penn and Princeton, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Women's Ice Hockey, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Basketball v. Lafayette, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Women's Swimming v. Springfield, 1977 November (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - 1977 December 2-17
      - Strike settlement negotiations, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Grecian Urns Exhibit, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Hockey v. Cornell, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Fencing v. West Point, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Wrestling v. Rutgers, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Hockey v. Colgate, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Squash v. Amherst, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Swimming v. S. Conn, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Women's Ice Hockey v. Brown, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Wrestling v. Army, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Women's Swimming v. U Mass, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Hockey v. Brown, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Women's Basketball v. Penn, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Basketball v. Holy Cross, 1977 December (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - 1978
    - 1978 January 4-31
      - Sailing at NH yacht club, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Yale ski team, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Fencing v. Columbia, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Track v. Penn and Brown, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Basketball v. SCSC, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Women's Squash, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Men's Volleyball Practice, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Football v. Cornell, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Basketball v. Williams, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Hockey v. CC, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Swimming v. Penn, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Women's Gymnastics v. U Conn, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Women's Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Fencing, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Women's Basketball v. Fordham, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Women's Swimming v. Dartmouth, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Hockey v. Clarkson, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Basketball v. Columbia, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Basketball v. Cornell, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Swimming v. Cornell, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Wrestling, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - 1978 February 1-27
      - Walter Camp Awards, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Women's Swimming, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Squash v. Trinity, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Women meeting in JE, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Squash v. Navy, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Women's Squash, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Men's Squash Head Shots, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Hockey v. Penn, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Hockey v. U Conn, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Basketball v. Penn, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Basketball v. Princeton, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Hockey v. BU, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Wrestling v. Navy, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Gymnastics v. Penn, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Women's Basketball v. Penn, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Women's Basketball v. Harvard, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Basketball v. Brown, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Squash v. Harvard, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Men's All Ivy Gymnastics, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1978 February (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - 1978 March 2 - April 27
      - Track victory, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Princeton Wins Home Cup, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Basketball v. Harvard, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Lighhtweight Crew v. DV and Frish, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Lightweight Crew v. Varsity, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Baseball v. Trinity, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Women's Lacrosse, Swimming, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Women's Lacrosse Head Shots, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Sheffield, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Varsity Golf, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - 5th floor Basketball, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. N Eastern, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Women's Softball v. Fairfield, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Women's Tennis v. Princeton, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Women's Tennis v. Harvard, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Women's Crew v. Dartmouth, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Men's Lacrosse v. Army, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Brown, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Tennis, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Synchronized Swimming, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Baseball v. Fairfield, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Basketball v. Columbia, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - 1978 May 3-18
      - Scholars at the House, 1978 May (Box 7, Folder 80)
      - Baseball v. Harvard, 1978 May (Box 7, Folder 80)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Harvard, 1978 May (Box 7, Folder 80)
      - Tennis v. Harvard, 1978 May (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - 1978 September 5-30
      - Standing alone, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Standing alone-sunny day, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Football v. CW Post, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Soccer v. Serimmago, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Rugby v. Manhattan, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Practices at Bowl, Soccer v. Field Hockey, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Football intersquad Scrimmage, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Soccer v. Sacred Heart, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Football v. U Conn, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Field Hockey, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Soccer v. U Mass, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Football v. Brown, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Field Hockey v. Springfield, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Water Polo v. Trinity, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Football v. U Conn, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Water Polo, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Field Hockey v. Williams, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Soccer v. UNH, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Cross Country v. Brown, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - 1978 October 7-30
      - Standing alone, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Standing alone-motorcyclist on sidewalk, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Cross Country- HYP, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Intramural sports- parents weekend, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Monkey costume, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Football v. Rutgers, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Soccer v. Army, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Men's Cross Country v. Columbia and Dartmouth, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Women's Volleyball v. Brown and Sacred Heart, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Women's Soccer v. Smith, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Intramural Soccer JE/Stiles, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Intramural Football JE/Branford, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Women's Soccer v. Dartmouth, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Men's Soccer v. Dartmouth, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Football v. Columbia, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Field Hockey, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Women's Soccer v. SCSC, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Women's Field Hockey v. Conn Col., 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Soccer v. Columbia, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Women's Soccer v. Wesleyan, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Football v. Army, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Volleyball Tournament, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Football v. Penn, 1978 October (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - 1978 November 1-28
      - Yoga Class, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Helmets(?), 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Judo Practice, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Basketball Practice, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Soccer v. Cornell, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Football v. Cornell, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Women's Volleyball, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Morse/Stiles Track; Football v. TD Silliman, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Penn Football, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Football v. Princeton, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Soccer v. Princeton, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Rugby v. Princeton, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Women's Soccer v. Harvard, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Football v. Harvard, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Field Hockey v. Harvard, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Rugby v. Harvard, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Intramural Basketball, Volleyball, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Women's Filed Hockey v. Harvard, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Hockey v. Princeton, 1978 November (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - 1978 December 2-12
      - Basketball v. U Conn, 1978 December (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Women's Basketball v. U Conn, 1978 December (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Women's Hockey v. U Conn, 1978 December (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Men's Gymnastics v. Coast Guard, 1978 December (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Women's Basketball v. Providence College, 1978 December (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Swimming v. Columbia, 1978 December (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Squash v. Stony Brook, 1978 December (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Basketball v. Brown, 1978 December (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - 1979
    - 1979 January 16-31
      - Chess team, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Judo, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Michael-Chess Champ, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Super Bowl specs, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Cocaine exhibition at Yale Med. School Library, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Hockey v. RPI, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Basketball v. Navy, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Squash, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Squash v. Dartmouth, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Hockey v. Cornell, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Fencing v. RI, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Wrestling v. Temple, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Women's Squash v. Williams, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Swimming v. Army, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Women's' Squash v. Wesleyan, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Women's Swimming v. Manhattan, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Basketball v. Cornell, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Squash v. Penn, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Basketball v. Columbia, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Women's Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Gymnastics v. MIT, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Women's Hockey v. Wesleyan, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Hockey v. New Prep, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Basketball v. Seton Hall, 1979 January (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - 1979 February 3-28
      - Howe Cup, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Women's Athletics dinner at commons, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Standing alone- girl in laundry room, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Head shaving, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Hockey v. VT, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Hockey v. UVM, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Volleyball v. West Point, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Women's Hockey v. BU, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Basketball v. Penn, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Gymnastics, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Basketball v. Princeton, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Women's Swimming v. Rutgers, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - JE Sux v. Davenport Hockey, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Squash v. Army, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Swimming, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Women's Squash v. Vassar, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Squash v. Princeton, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Track v. Cornell, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Hockey v. Brown andUVM-Misc, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Basketball v. Harvard, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Swimming v. Dartmouth, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Men's Volleyball v. Delaware, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Women's Basketball, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Wrestling v. Harvard, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Basketball v. Union College, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Women's Basketball v. Brown, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Swimming v. Princeton, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Women's Basketball v. OWA, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Basketball v. Dartmouth, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Basketball V. Harvard, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Women's Squash v. Princeton, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Hockey v. North Eastern, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Women's Gymnastics v. Conn College, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Soccer v. Penn, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Tang Cup Hockey Championships, 1979 February (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - 1979 March 1-31
      - Winter sports special, 1979 March (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Rabbits, 1979 March (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Tang Cup Championship, 1979 March (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Women's Crew Practice, 1979 March (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Women's tennis, 1979 March (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Hockey v. Harvard, 1979 March (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Women's Hockey v. Princeton, 1979 March (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Hockey v. UNH, 1979 March (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Lacrosse v. S. Conn, 1979 March (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Lacrosse v. U Conn, 1979 March (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Track, 1979 March (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - 1979 April 4-29
      - Yale Crew, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Skeet Shooting, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Tang Competition (TD v. SM), 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Conn, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Women's lacrosse v. U Mass, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Women's Track v. Brown, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Baseball v. Hopkins, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Men's Lacrosse v. Columbia, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Baseball v. Wesleyan, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Trinity, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Tennis v. Princeton, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Women's lacrosse v. Penn, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Lacrosse v. Princeton, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Empty Baseball Field, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Baseball v. Springfield, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Women's Lacrosse v. Brown, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Intramural Cross Country, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Tennis v. Army, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Baseball v. Army, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Crew v. Penn, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Men's Lacrosse, 1979 April (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - 1979 May 13
      - Sprints, 1979 May (Box 8, Folder 89)
      - Messy Rooms, 1979 May (Box 8, Folder 89)
      - Moving, 1979 May (Box 8, Folder 89)
      - Payne Whitney Interior, 1979 May (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - 1979 September 9-29
      - Branford tag-standing alone, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - ABC Sports, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Freshman Soccer Scrimmage, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Field Hockey Practice, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Women's Field Hockey Practice, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Football v. BU, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Water Polo, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Soccer, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Football Scrimmage, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Soccer v. Seattle, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Football Practice, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Soccer v. South Hampton, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Field Hockey v. Montclair, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Crew v. Penn, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Football v. Brown, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Women's Field Hockey v. Brown, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Rugby v. Boston College, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Soccer v. Brown, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Baseball, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Soccer v. S Conn, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Football v. U Conn, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Football memorabilia, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Soccer v. Tel Aviv, 1979 September (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - 1979 October 3-31
      - Music Convention, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - "Dan" drinking beer and pre-game standing alone, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Dr. Pelside-Nobel Winner, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Cricket, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Intramural Sports, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Marathon runner, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Volleyball v. New Haven, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Water Polo Championships, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Field Hockey v. RI, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Water Polo v. BU, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Football v. Colgate, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Water Polo v. Harvard, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Football v. Brown, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Baseball, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Women's Cross Country, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Soccer v. Brown, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Women's Soccer v. Dartmouth, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Football v. Dartmouth, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Soccer v. Dartmouth, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Field Hockey v. Dartmouth, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Team and Individual Portraits, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Varsity Field Hockey, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Field Hockey v. Bridgewater, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Football v. Columbia, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Crew: Head of Charles Regatta, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Soccer v. Springfield, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Women's Field Hockey v. SCSC, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Bladderball, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Football v. Penn, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - Soccer v. Penn, 1979 October (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - 1979 November 2-30
      - Women's Field Hockey, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Football v. Cornell, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Soccer v. Fairfield, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Volleyball, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Soccer v. Princeton, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Steve Eddy (Angel's Pitcher), 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Football v. Princeton, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - Intramural teams v. Harvard, 1979 November (Box 9, Folder 92)